# **Berat Kales**

## **Professional Summary**

Adelphi University undergrad with an interest in careers in software engineering. I excel in working collaboratively with others whether it be on the field, in the classroom, or in the workplace. My ability to adapt to foreign experiences as well as my hard work and commitment allow me to tackle any task or challenge that lies ahead of me.

## Work Experience

### Wild Fig - Lake Success, NY

#### Server/Crew

2/2020 - 7/2020

Helping and serving customers, preparing food, stocking food and supplies, prepping and closing.

#### Adelphi University - Admissions Assistant

10/2019 - Present

As a Freshman, I was able to successfully make guests at Adelphi University feel welcome. Throughout my time, I have contributed by organizing signage, checking guests in, and greeting guests as they tour the campus.

## Village of Mineola - Summer Rec Counselor

07/2018 - 08/2019

I have worked as a summer rec counselor for two years and it has been a wonderful experience for both of them. I was able to keep the children I had engaged and I have made these past two summers very memorable for the kids and my co-counselors.

#### Achievements:

- Varsity football and lacrosse
- High School Robotics
- Summer Camp Counselor
- First Year Community Action
  Program(FCAP) at Adelphi
- Mineola Macaroni(Fundraiser for soup kitchen)

## Education:

- Graduated Mineola High School
- Currently enrolled at Adelphi
  University, majoring in Computer
  Science

#### Contact:

- bkales123@gmail.com
- (516) 427-0496